both: I heart the circus!
两人：我喜欢马戏团！
- Children of all ages!
- 所有年龄段的孩子！
Get ready to wet
your baggy pants laughing!
准备好淋湿
你的宽松裤子在笑！
Send in the clowns!
派小丑来！
He-yah!
嘿-呀！
Our candy-corn-fed clowns
我们以糖果玉米喂养的小丑
once roamed
the slapstick plains
曾经漫游过
闹剧平原
where wild clowns run free!
狂野的小丑在那里自由奔跑！
* *
**
He-yah!
嘿-呀！
* *
**
He-yah!
嘿-呀！
[donkey brays,
balloon swells, pops]
[驴叫声，
气球膨胀，爆裂]
- Look, there's those!
- 看，就是那些！
- Oh.
- 哦。
Are you hungry, little clown?
小小丑，你饿了吗？
- He-yah!
- 嘿啊！
Don't feed the clowns!
不要喂小丑！
SpongeBob, are you mad?
海绵宝宝，你生气了吗？
Clowns are dangerous animals.
小丑是危险的动物。
Why, at any moment,
one of those things
为什么，在任何时候，
其中之一
could get loose
and bite our feet off!
可能会松动
并咬掉我们的脚！
- Oh, Patrick, that little
clown wouldn't do that.
- 哦，帕特里克，那个小
小丑不会这么做。
He was friendly.
他很友善。
* *
**
I wanna go backstage
and see the clowns, Patrick.
我想去后台
看看小丑，帕特里克。
- I told you, SpongeBob,
our feet are in danger!
- 我告诉过你了，海绵宝宝，
我们的脚有危险！
- I'll protect you.
- 我会保护你。
Ooh.
哦。
* *
**
clowns: Huh?
小丑：啊？
- Poor little guy.
- 可怜的小家伙。
- Hey, he didn't get any food.
- 嘿，他没有得到任何食物。
Hmm.
唔。
- Hey, psst!
- 嘿，嘘！
Huh?
啊？
- Don't feed the clowns!
- 不要喂小丑！
- My feet!
- 我的脚！
- Pack it up, everyone.
- 收拾好，大家。
He-yah!
嘿-呀！
* *
**
- I don't care what that mean
old ringmaster says.
- 我不在乎这意味着什么
老领班说道。
That clown is hungry, and I'm
gonna feed him.
那个小丑饿了，而我
会喂他。
Hey, where'd the circus go?
嘿，马戏团去哪儿了？
Now I'll never find that little
clown.
现在我再也找不到那个小东西了
小丑。
There you are.
你就在那里。
- Hey, little clown.
- 嘿，小小丑。
The circus left without you!
马戏团离开了你！
Quick, we gotta get you back to
your clown friends.
快点，我们得送你回去
你的小丑朋友。
Oh, you don't want to go
back to the circus?
哦，你不想走
回到马戏团？
- You don't want to be
a circus clown?
- 你不想成为
马戏团小丑？
- You know, little clown,
I don't blame you.
- 你知道，小小丑，
我不怪你。
You shouldn't stay in a place
where they
你不应该呆在一个地方
他们在哪里
push you around
all the time.
把你推来推去
一直。
Looks like I'll have to help
you find a new job.
看来我得帮忙
你找到了一份新工作。
But what else can you do?
但你还能做什么呢？
- This job should be a snap,
little clown.
- 这项工作应该是轻而易举的，
小小丑。
Watch me.
看着我。
* Pick up the hot dog,
put it in a bun *
*拿起热狗，
把它放进包子里*
* Add the mustard, relish,
now you're having fun *
*加入芥末，调味，
现在你玩得很开心*
- Oh-ho-ho, hotdog!
- 哦嗬嗬，热狗！
Look at that.
看看那个。
Looks like fun!
看起来很有趣！
- Okay, you're on.
- 好吧，你开始了。
[hotdogs hissing,
clown screams]
[热狗嘶嘶作响，
小丑尖叫]
My wieners!
我的维也纳人！
Sorry.
对不起。
I think you'll get a job
a lot quicker
我想你会找到工作的
快很多
if we tone down the whole
clown thing a smidge.
如果我们调低整体
小丑的事有点。
Don't worry.
When I get through with you,
不用担心。
当我和你相处的时候
your own ringmaster
won't recognize you.
你自己的领班
不会认出你的。
Ahh!
啊！
- "Businessmen wanted."
——《商人通缉》。
Go get 'em, little clown.
去抓住他们吧，小小丑。
Oh, I mean, Mr. little clown.
哦，我是说，小小丑先生。
- Here's your stool.
Here's your stamper.
- 这是你的凳子。
这是你的印章。
Now get to work.
现在开始工作吧。
- Aww.
- 哇。
Who hired this clown?
谁雇了这个小丑？
- Um, you did, sir.
- 嗯，你做到了，先生。
Fired!
被解雇了！
What happened, little clown?
发生什么事了，小小丑？
Didn't you like that job?
你不喜欢那份工作吗？
- Hmm.
- 唔。
Ooh!
哦！
Maybe a career in firefighting.
也许从事消防工作。
- Have a nice fire!
- 祝你生火愉快！
I'll just make sure he gets
there safely.
我会确保他得到
安全地在那里。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇。
Not Mrs. Puff's Boating School!
不是帕夫夫人的划船学校！
- Save me!
Save me!
- 救救我！
救救我吧！
I'm too young to broil!
我太年轻了，不能烤！
You're fired!
你被解雇了！
- This is it, little clown.
- 就是这样，小小丑。
The last job available in
Bikini Bottom.
最后一个职位是在
比基尼下装。
- If you can just stop
the clowning for two minutes,
- 如果你能停下来
两分钟的小丑表演，
you'll have a job.
你会有一份工作。
Please!
请！
Sorry, little clown.
It's been a long day.
对不起，小小丑。
这是漫长的一天。
Good luck.
祝你好运。
Hmm.
唔。
Aha!
啊哈！
Now get in there, eyes,
现在进入那里，眼睛，
and stay close to that clown.
并靠近那个小丑。
- Your job
is to pack up the pies!
- 你的工作
就是收拾馅饼！
- Hmm!
- 唔！
- No! No, little clown!
No!
- 不！不，小小丑！
不！
No!
Phew!
唷！
- Lemon pie!
- 柠檬派！
- Mmm!
- 嗯！
- Eye pie!
- 眼睛馅饼！
You...
你...
Are...
是...
Au revoir!
再见！
I didn't order a pie.
我没有点馅饼。
- Oh, little clown,
I'm so sorry.
- 哦，小小丑，
我很抱歉。
I thought you needed a day job,
but you're a clown.
我以为你需要一份日常工作
但你是个小丑。
And a clown needs to run free.
小丑需要自由奔跑。
[clowns laughing
and chattering]
[小丑笑
和喋喋不休]
- Aww.
- 哇。